<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dark Heresy</title>
    <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dark Heresy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 09-22 [Matt Keathley](https://www.keathley.co)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 21:33:36 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.darkheresy.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chance Reed</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/chance-reed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 21:33:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/chance-reed/</guid>
      <description>Name: Chance Reed
Homeworld: Highborn
Career: Rogue Trader Fleet Desperado
Gender: Male
Build: Fit
Skin Color: Tan
Hair Color: Grey
Eye Color: Green
Age: Prime
Quirk: None
Divination: A suspicious mind is a healthy mind.
Back Story:
Chance spent a decade on the Rogue Trade ship The Harlan serving as a pilot and attendant to various officers. Having won his way aboard the ship in a dice game he had to work extra hard to earn the respect of the rest of the ships crew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 33.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-33-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:10:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-33-5/</guid>
      <description>The acolytes are in the room with the dead bodies with a Janissairie having turned on his brother. There is a bit of uncertainty in the air about how to continue.
Tertius Tertius watches the raving Janissary get cuffed and tranquilized. Deep in though he walks over to where Servius is by the body of the man in the chair. He whispers to Servius as he starts to search the body, &amp;ldquo;Let us hope these are not our friends from the Ordo Malleus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 32.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-32-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:01:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-32-5/</guid>
      <description>Tertius Servius&amp;rsquo; chuckle at Aleister calls attention towards the young man. Tertius, sitting near Aleister asks him in low, concerned tones, &amp;ldquo;Sir. Is everything quite alright? You seem somewhat distressed.&amp;rdquo;
Aleister &amp;ldquo;I.. Uh&amp;hellip; what do you mean?&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Aleister starts becoming quite flustered and furthers avoiding eye contact.
Tertius Tertius makes a calming gesture with his hand towards Aleister (a patting motion), &amp;ldquo;Please do not be troubled sir. I apologize on Servius&amp;rsquo; behalf for his treatment of you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 31.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-31-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 10:36:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-31-5/</guid>
      <description>With the daemon freed to wander amongst the stars, the storm breaks within the city of Sinophia Manga and washes away the blood from the streets for now. Constantine musters his strength and takes over what remains of the Adeptus Arbites force, calling in his scant reinforcements Karib City and sending a distress call to his subsector command. Meetings are held and after learning of Skarmen&amp;rsquo;s infamy &amp;ndash; even if the common people never do &amp;ndash; the Undertow and the Enforcers alike rein in their forces for the time being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 30.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-30-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:36:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-30-5/</guid>
      <description>Tertius Tertius holsters the bolt pistol in his shoulder harness and then produces a small cleaning cloth. He busies himself with wiping away the gore from his glasses and says, &amp;ldquo;All of you stay on your guard. That corpse thrall comtinued to attack after Skarmen was deceased so whatever is empowering those abominations still remains.&amp;rdquo;
He puts the less bloody glasses on, shakes the cloth out and puts it away. He then stoops down to search Skarmen&amp;rsquo;s pockets while saying to Fihad, &amp;ldquo;Marshall Constantine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 29.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-29-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 21:22:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-29-5/</guid>
      <description>Tertius examines the bodies of the thralls, both torn into two from the barrage of bullets and internal explosions, looking for clues. As he ponders what it would take such a heretical being the arbiter vox is active with details about attacks around the city.
Garbled reports start to come through of an attack on an Enforcer column moving through the commercia ambushed by an unknown force. Rapidly, things worsen: some reports claim that the Khan himself has been killed in the attack, others suggest that he is critically injured or even taken captive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 28.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-28-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 21:44:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-28-5/</guid>
      <description>Theta and Servius exit the manor by the main gates. Servius is still catching his breath from the hit he took and his quick exit. Behind some shrubs near the entrance Eupheme watches hesitantly. &amp;ldquo;Were you able to stop the attack? Are we safe?&amp;rdquo; Theta nods and heads back inside leaving Servius to rest with Eupheme.
Exploring the remainder of House Amorite is a lesson in decay. It has become an ancient pile filled with cobwebs and spoiled grandeur surrounded by an overgrown garden of weeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 27.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-27-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 20:32:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-27-5/</guid>
      <description>A respite from the fight emerges as the final attacker falls to the floor in flames. The court is still hot from battle and the burning corpses that litter the floor. From within the halls, the panic can be heard as those left alive flee for their lives. Skarmen glances back at the Acolytes and urges, &amp;ldquo;Hurry, we must secure the Judiciary!&amp;rdquo; Tertius nods as he and Servius help Torqul to his feet and assist him out of the court and into the inner halls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 26.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-26-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 17:25:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-26-5/</guid>
      <description>Naeva You leave the Folly being careful to remain concealed as you sneak out and into the city. You make your way to the outside of District VII also known as the &amp;lsquo;Shadow Manses&amp;rsquo; but are aware as you approach that you have seen the manses dominate the skyline of the other districts. The seaward edge of District VII is protected from the worst of the elements by a sheer cliff that darkens its streets in shade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 25.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-25-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 20:15:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-25-5/</guid>
      <description>Tiber shrugs as Tertius asks about the &amp;ldquo;witch mirror&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;I have heard about similar things but don&amp;rsquo;t know much about them. Callisto, he was my old boss, he had a &amp;rsquo;truth glass&amp;rsquo; he claimed. I saw it, pretty thing, but I thought it was just a lie to fighten the dregs and other witless filth. However, word did reach me about the sacking at Worm&amp;rsquo;s End. It&amp;rsquo;s just an old canteen in district 13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 24.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-24-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 20:51:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-24-5/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It has to be the enforcers and if they want a war we are going to give it to them.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hesul sent us out yesterday. I was worried we would be stuck in that graveyard for the whole week!&amp;rdquo;
The motor skiff finally comes to a halt on an old wooden pier on the edge of the Commercia district. Georg and his gang disembark and beckon the acolytes to follow the group around a large building and through its massive doors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 23.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-23-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:06:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-23-5/</guid>
      <description>The man spins and with a pommel strike of the sword knock the shotgun free from Theta&amp;rsquo;s grip sending it flying till it slides across the cement roof into a corner.
Theta turns to known down the opponent.
Theta and the man began grappling with neither one immediately gaining the upper hand. Theta reels back during a particularly aggressive move and notices an opening thinking that she is about to be struck with the blade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 22.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-22-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 22:51:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-22-5/</guid>
      <description>Four days out from Quaddis on a rusty tramp freighter bound for Sinophia; the team finishes dinner in a deserted corner of the mess. The crew, having caught wind of the team&amp;rsquo;s inquisitorial ties, has given them a wide berth and are out of ear shot.
Tertius thoroughly wipes his mouth with a cloth napkin after the less than savory meal. He clears his throat in such a way as to be a polite call for attention and says, &amp;ldquo;Torqul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 7.6</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-7-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 14:58:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-7-6/</guid>
      <description>After the acolytes had finished conferring amongst themselves of the next course of action, they loaded up and left the Clockwork Court. Leaving the building there is a clear sense of anxiety amongst the remaining workers. It is a palpable concern that makes it clear that nothing profitable will be accomplished today. The same feeling extends upon leaving the building. The news of the governmental attack and perhaps even the death of the Judiciary has spread faster than anyone could have anticipated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 7.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-7-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 22:52:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-7-5/</guid>
      <description>Dezner &amp;ldquo;After we finish at the crime scene, I suggest that we split into two groups. One group can take care of contacting the criminal underworld and shopping, and the other can head back to base to get Tertius fixed up and any samples analyzed.&amp;rdquo;
Tactitus &amp;ldquo;Tacitus agrees with Dezner. Since Servius has more experience with the investigative aspects needed, I feel he should accompany Tertius. I can tag loosely behind Dezner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 7.4</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-7-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 17:23:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-7-4/</guid>
      <description>In his downtime Tacitus sought to aquire ostentatious and deadly possessions, aligning with his new aggressive philosophy. Also, he began the visual metamorphosis that had already taken place within himself while on Quaddis. The Acolyte looks much different than the young man who assisted you on Acreage or the Ghost Ship. That man had the cocksure manner of a well-to-do noble accompanied with the fiery zeal of his youth. However that time has passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 5.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-5-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 14:18:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-5-5/</guid>
      <description>The Acolytes have scored a great victory over the servants of Chaos and bested evil where it may be found. The extraordinary eclipse swiftly passes with the Widower’s bodily destruction and light once again shines on Xicarph, leaving the Acolytes amid the carnage of the great and good. It is not long before armed servitors manage to regain control of the manse from the Pilgrim’s grasp. Entering the Theater of Clocks the usher your group of wounded and weary from the estate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 3.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-3-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 11:27:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-3-5/</guid>
      <description>The universe is a dangerous place- your retinue has experienced this first hand on multiple occasions. But this particular experience has begun to take it&amp;rsquo;s toll. You have all fought for survival on multiple occasions in the past 48 hours and it creates a somber atmosphere in Septimus&amp;rsquo; small sectional. Dezner and Tertius manage to carry in the wounded and see to their immediate needs but eventually what is required is simple rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 2.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-2-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 19:48:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/session-2-5/</guid>
      <description>As everyone is milling around the White Scholars small home, Tacitus turns to Septimus and asks, &amp;ldquo;Would it be agreeable with you to go back to the Libraries tonight? While we could all use some rest I find myself restless.&amp;rdquo;
Septimus responds, &amp;ldquo;Perhaps - although it is getting late. May I ask what you wish to seek tonight?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;As you well know, knowledge is power. There is a lot more going on here with this festival than we have a grasp on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Trader - 3.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/rogue-trader-3-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 13:22:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/rogue-trader-3-5/</guid>
      <description>Port Wander The shipyard reports indicate that the ship will be completely repaired and refitted in two weeks time. Much had been accomplished by the crew of the (what did you rename the ship Micah?) but some important tasks still needed to be attended to before the end of the repairs.
Cadmus A summons from your brother comes to you one afternoon while you are looking over the ships books with Hycler, your new purser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Trader - 2.5</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/rogue-trader-2-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 15:26:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/rogue-trader-2-5/</guid>
      <description>Josh 044.861.M41
Aboard the Hazeroth-class raider “the Throat Slitter” (formerly the Zephyr)
Navigator Yorke Benetek raises wearily but successfully from the navigation station of the Slitter’s still bloody bridge. He had just translated the former pirate raider and the accompanying Fortunatus, into warp space. The path ahead seems clear and the currents of the warp seem favorable for a swift return to Port Wander. Tybalt Gath also moves away from the ship’s helm, allowing a crewman to take his position after over 10 hours piloting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From the Journal of Tacitus Gath</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/tacitus-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 22:57:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/tacitus-journal/</guid>
      <description>Excerpt from Private Journal of Tacitus Gath: Tacitus Gath: The Glory of Madness I have seen it now, the way of things. The God-Emperor gives us what we can take and then he gives us more without ceasing until we shatter like a chandelier smiting the ballroom floor. But He-enthroned does not leave us in this state. No, the God-Emperor reconstitutes us from the ashes of our humanity.
He makes us stronger than before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From the Journal of Tertius Kabakes</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/tertius-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 22:57:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/stories/tertius-journal/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 of my first mission. The Brazen Sky. At last we have completed our training. No more grueling physical training and endless indoctrination. I must confess a mounting excitement at the prospect of venturing out on my first mission. For posterity’s sake I have decided to keep a journal to chronicle my future voyages.
Currently I am aboard the freighter “Brazen Sky”, bound for Iocanthos. Inquisitor Graves has personally assigned the group and me to investigate some strange occurrences that have be reported at the building site for a new cathedral dedicated to the great saint Drusus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servius Flavion</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/servius-flavion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2009 02:04:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/servius-flavion/</guid>
      <description>Name: Servius Flavion
Homeworld: Schola Progenium
Career: Arbitrator
Rank: Trooper
Gender: Male
Build: Well-built
Skin Color: Tan
Hair Color: Shaven
Eye Color: Blue
Age: 32
Quirk: You have a devotional scar.
Family&amp;rsquo;s Fate: Slaughtered by Rebels
Divination: If a job is worth doing it is worth dying for. (Frenzy talent)
Starting XP: 200
Starting Package: The Calixian Pattern Killings
Traits: Schola Education, Skill at Arms, Sheltered Upbringing, Tempered Will
Basic Skills: Common Lore (Administratum) (Int) (Sch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alaric Adranus</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/alaric-adranus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 22:57:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/alaric-adranus/</guid>
      <description>Name: Alaric Adranus
Homeworld: Battlefleet Calixis
Career: Imperial Psyker
Rank: Sanctionite
Gender: Male
Build: Gaunt
Skin Color: Fair
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Watery Blue
Age: 37
Quirk: None
Ship Tradition: War Ship
Divination: Know the mutant; kill the mutant.
Starting XP: 400
Starting Package: None
Traits: Shipwise, Void Accustomed, Naval Lineage Skills, Close-Quarter Fighter, Officer on Deck, Sanctioned Psyker
Basic Skills: Navigation (Stellar) (Int) (Shipwise), Pilot (Starcraft) (Ag) (Shipwise), Common Lore (Tech) (Int) (Nav.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tacitus Gath</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/tacitus-gath/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 17:46:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/tacitus-gath/</guid>
      <description>Name: Tacitus Gath
Homeworld/Sector: Scintilla/Calixis
Career: Cleric
Gender: Male
Build: Fit (1.6m/60kg)
Skin: pale
Hair: blonde
Eyes: Grey
Age: 25
Divination: “Only in death does duty end” +1 wound
Starting XP: 400
Starting Package: Redemptionist Firebrand
Talents/Traits: Melee Weapon Training (Primitive, Chain,), Pistol Training (SP), Thrown Weapon Training (Primitive), Etiquette (+10 Charm, Deceive, and Scrutiny when dealing with authority), Supremely Connected (Military), Peer (Nobility, Military), Unshakable Faith
Basic Skills: Intimidate (S), Interrogation (WP)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siskon Hratul</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/siskon-hratul/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 12:13:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/siskon-hratul/</guid>
      <description>Name: Siskon Hratul
Homeworld: Forge World (Demesne-type) &amp;ndash; Faith in destiny and ability to overcome whatever fate brings: the weak perish and the superior survive.
Career: Tech-Priest
Rank: Technographer
Gender: Male
Build: Wiry (1.75m/65kg)
Skin Color: Stained (pale, but with metallic tinted patches)
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Lenses (Red)
Age: 22
Quirk: Electoo
Divination: ?
Starting XP: 300 (600 minus 300 for starting package)
Starting Package: The Divine Light of Sollex [-5 Fellowship, +1d5 Insanity points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tertius Kabakes</title>
      <link>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/tertius-kabakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 01:27:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.darkheresy.co/acolytes/tertius-kabakes/</guid>
      <description>Name:	Tertius Kabakes
Homeworld:	Imperial World - Maccabeus Quintus
Career:	Adept
Rank:	Archivist
Gender:	Male
Build:	Svelte
Skin Color:	Fair
Hair Color:	Brown
Eye Color:	Green
Age:	29
Quirk:	None
Planet of Birth:	Maccabeus Quintus
Divination:	Die if you must, but not with your spirit broken.
Starting XP:	400 (+400 from Matt)
Starting Package:	None
Traits: Blessed Ignorance, Hagiography, Litugical Familiarity, Barren World, Beloved of the God-Emperor
Basic Skills: Common Lore (Imperial Creed) (Int) (Hagi.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
